Carlos Davila

Location: Los Angeles

inkedin.com/in/carlos-alexis-davila

shadezs.github.io

https://github.com/Shadezs

davila salazar carlo@student.smc.edu

Summary

Software Engineer skilled in Unity(C#), Robotics(C, C++), VEX, Android Development. Experienced Teacher with a demonstrated history of working in the primary/secondary education industry. Currently pursuing an Associate's degree in Computer Science from Santa Monica College intending to transfer to a four-year university.

Experience



Snap Engineering Academy Scholar

Snap Inc

Jul 2020 - Present

- Developed multiple websites using HTML, CSS and different JavaScript frameworks
- Leveraged Snap-kit to create an online game on Glitch
- Participated in fireside chats and mentorships with Snap Inc. employees
- Managed and collaborated with an intern development team to prototype a new Snap
 Mini application
- Presented Hackathon project to a panel of seniors Engineers



Robotics and Programming Teacher

STEAM Bot Workshop

Apr 2017 - Present

- Teach and develop programming curriculum for 5th-12th-grade and basic game design through Scratch, Unity, Processing, and Minecraft Modding
- Programming coach for four VEX robotics competition teams (Two teams made to state finals)
- Wrote driver-control and autonomous script for robotic competitions using Python, Robot
 C, and C++

Education



Santa Monica College

Associate's degree, Computer Science

2017 - 2021

Leadership

• Co-Founder and President of the Robotics Club at Santa Monica College

2018 - Present

Skills

• C• C++ • Python • GIT • Robotics • Unity • Java • JavaScript • C# • Linux